CLÉMENT HENNEBELLE

■ CLEMENT.HENNEBELLE@HOTMAIL.FR

+1 514-583-2767

MONTRÉAL, QC

SUMMARY

After an initial career in the digital field, I chose to shift my focus by pursuing musical training, which allowed me to develop creative and technical skills. Today, I aim to restart my career in video game development by deepening my technical knowledge. With several years of experience working in digital and video game projects, I have gained solid expertise in engines such as Unity and Unreal Engine. Currently training in GLSL via Touch Designer, I am also developing skills in graphic programming. My various experiences, both in the digital field and other sectors, have allowed me to adapt to diverse environments and teams. I prioritize cohesion in group projects and place great deal of importance on the quality of the delivered work.

EDUCATION

Université de Montréal

Majeure Musiques numériques 2024

CONCORDIA UNIVERSITY

Bachelor's Computer Science 2019 Video games option

EMPLOYMENT

BEHAVIOUR INTERACTIVE

Montréal, QC

Juil. 2019 à Janv. 2020

- GAMEPLAY PROGRAMMER

 Unreal Engine 5 experience
- Gameplay programming for an online game (network handling)
- Al programming for gameplay purposes

PLAYMIND Montréal, QC

GAMEPLAY AND TECHNOLOGIES PROGRAMMER

AVR. 2018 À AOÛT 2021

- Unity 3D experience
- Worked on several numerical installation projects, from programming to on-site installation
- Collaborated with several art specialties, integrating their work into the final product

PROJECTS

PORTFOLIO WEBSITE

Portfolio website gathering projects in my different areas of work. Programmed in Typescript using the React framework.

www.clementhennebelle.com

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES: C++, C#, GLSL

LANGUAGES: Français, English

SOFTWARES: Unreal Engine 5, Unity, Touch Designer, Perforce, Git

VOLUNTEERING

GANG DE DEVS (GROUPE ASSOCIATIF POUR LA NOUVELLE GÉNÉRATION DE DÉVELOPPEURS)

SEPT. 2018 À Août 2021

· ADMINISTRATOR

Montréal, QC

Organized and led monthly events with students and young professionals. Those events gave the opportunity to industry newcomers to meet veterans, and to get a better feel of life within the video game world.